[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city is the capital of Madagascar?", "correct_answer": "Antananarivo", "incorrect_answers": ["Toamasina", "Harare", "Maputo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to a survey, what percentage of American cat owners admit to blow drying their feline after giving it a bath?", "correct_answer": "25%", "incorrect_answers": ["15%", "70%", "5%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of Ralphies family in The Christmas Story?", "correct_answer": "Parker", "incorrect_answers": ["Cleveland", "McGavin", "Peterson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although almost non-existent today, what ancient religion, stemming predominantly from Persia, worshipped Ahura Mazda as an uncreated Creator and God.", "correct_answer": "Zoroastrianism", "incorrect_answers": ["Hinduism", "Rastafarianism", "Taoism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of the atoms mass is concentrated in its nucleus?", "correct_answer": "99.9 %", "incorrect_answers": ["90 %", "70 %", "0,01 %"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the state flower of Maryland?", "correct_answer": "Black-eyed Susan", "incorrect_answers": ["Mountain Laurel", "Peach Blossom", "Flowering Dogwood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Vice President under President Dwight D. Eisenhower, when the Alaska Statehood Act was signed?", "correct_answer": "Richard Nixon", "incorrect_answers": ["Nelson  A Rockafeller", "Brian V Mitchell", "John L Truman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What first lady was the famous cousin of the daughter living at Grey Gardens?", "correct_answer": "Jacqueline Kennedy", "incorrect_answers": ["Eleanor Roosevelt", "Mamie Eisenhower", "Nancy Reagan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What record did the 2007 movie Pirates of the Caribbean: At Worlds End set at the time of its release?", "correct_answer": "Most expensive movie of all time", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Highest-grossing movie of all time", "Movie with the most Academy Award nominations"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first guest star to step off the plane on Fantasy Island?", "correct_answer": "Bill Bixby", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Knots", "Roddy McDowell", "Victoria Principal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On his third voyage to the Western hemisphere, Columbus wrote that he found where the Garden of Eden was. What do we now call the area which Columbus felt was the Garden of Eden ?", "correct_answer": "Venezuela", "incorrect_answers": ["Costa Rica", "Nassau", "Haiti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first hotdog stand in New York was opened in 1867.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]